freebiepixels.com 2012-06-22

# Privacy | Free Design Resources & PSD Files by Awesome Designers

Your privacy is critically important to us. At Freebie Pixels we have a few fundamental principles:  
1\. We don’t ask you for personal information unless we truly need it.  
2\. We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.  
3\. We don’t store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of one of our services.  
Below is our privacy policy which incorporates these goals:  
Cazoobi Creative Solutions operates freebiepixels.com. It is Cazoobi Creative Solutions policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect whilst operating our websites.

#### Website Visitors

Freebie Pixels collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Freebie Pixels purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Freebie Pixels visitors use its website. From time to time, Freebie Pixels may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g. by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.  
Freebie Pixels also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. Freebie Pixels does not use such information to identify its visitors, however, and does not disclose such information, other than under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information, as described below.

#### Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to Freebie Pixels choose to interact with Freebie Pixels in ways that require Freebie Pixels to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Freebie Pixels gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who create an account at freebiepixels.com to provide a username and email address. Freebie Pixels collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitors interaction with Freebie Pixels. Freebie Pixels does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

#### Aggregated Statistics

Freebie Pixels may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. Freebie Pixels may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Freebie Pixels does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

#### Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

Freebie Pixels discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Freebie Pixels behalf or to provide services available at the Freebie Pixels website, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using the Freebie Pixels website, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Freebie Pixels will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Freebie Pixels discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law, or when Freebie Pixels believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Freebie Pixels, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an Freebie Pixels website and have supplied your email address, Freebie Pixels may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with whats going on with Freebie Pixels and our products. We primarily use our various product blogs to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Freebie Pixels takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

#### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitors computer, and that the visitors browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Freebie Pixels uses cookies to help Freebie Pixels identify and track visitors, their usage of Freebie Pixels website, and their website access preferences. Freebie Pixels visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using the Freebie Pixels websites, with the drawback that certain features of the Freebie Pixels websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

#### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Freebie Pixels may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Freebie Pixels sole discretion. Freebie Pixels encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Freebie Pixels. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

This Terms of Service is crafted from [wordpress.com’s version](http://en.wordpress.com/tos/), which is available under a Creative Commons Sharealike license.
